http://www.hallplas.co.uk/privacy-policy

Contact
Website Privacy PolicyBelow, we have provided a summary of the ways in which we collect personal data from the users of this website and your rights regarding this data.For further information please contact us.SECTION 1 - PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USEWhen you contact us, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name and email address.When you browse our website, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.Personal data is used by us for secondary business activities, such as self-advertising, accounts and records. Data is only passed on to third parties to aid these activities (such as search engine optimisation and website usage monitoring etc) and is never sold or disclosed to external bodies for their own purposes.SECTION 2 - CONSENTHow do you get my consent?When you provide us with personal information as part of an enquiry,  you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.A cookie notice is also used to obtain your consent when you first visit our website. More information on cookies can be found in 'Section 7 - Cookies'.If we ask for your personal information for further use, such as marketing, we will provide a positive opt-in for your consent.How do I withdraw my consent?If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you and for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us using the button below:
Contact Us
or by mail at G-Mach Engineering Ltd: 7, 9 & 9a Beler Way, Leicester Rd Ind. Est. Melton Mowbray, Leicestershire, LE13 0DG, United KingdomSECTION 3 - DISCLOSUREWe may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.SECTION 4 - THIRD-PARTY SERVICESSquarespaceOur website is hosted on Squarespace. They provide us with the online platform that allows us to promote our services to customers.Personal data is processed with Squarespace’s storage, databases and software.Squarespace's Terms of Service and Privacy Statement can be found here:https://www.squarespace.com/terms-of-service/ https://www.squarespace.com/privacy/ Analytics ProvidersTo optimise search engine behaviour, our website may be linked with search analytics providers (Google Analytics and Bing Webmaster). Please review the terms and conditions of these third parties below:Google Policies:https://policies.google.com/Bing Policies:https://privacy.microsoft.com/ Fractal CGOur website is maintained by Fractal CG. As part of our website maintenance agreement, they have access to the Squarespace hosting and Analytics tools (previously described) in order to provide us with regular website performance updates.Fractal CG's Privacy Statement can be found here:https://fractalcg.com/privacy-policy/ In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.However, some third party service providers may have their own privacy policies regarding the information we provide them. Individuals should read the privacy policies of these providers to further understand the manner in which their personal information will be handled.Some providers may be located in or have systems that are located in a different jurisdiction to us. If so, an individual’s personal information may be subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which these systems are used.SECTION 5 - LINKSWhen you click links on our website, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.SECTION 6 - SECURITYTo protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.We use industry standard protection measures, such as secure passwords; SSL encryption; firewalls and more. However, no company, can fully eliminate the security risks associated with personal data storage.SECTION 7 - COOKIESOur website uses cookies and similar technologies to run and understand how visitors use the site. This data is collected automatically by Squarespace (the website host) and is used to monitor site traffic, usage patterns and analyse general demographic data. Some information is passed to analytics sites, including Google Analytics, to monitor data for search engine optimisation. Information is not used by us to identify individual users.To find out more please visit:https://www.squarespace.com/privacy/SECTION 10 - AGE OF CONSENTBy using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.SECTION 11 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICYWe reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.If our website is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners.QUESTIONS & CONTACT INFORMATIONIf you would like to: access, amend, transfer, restrict or delete any personal information we store about you; register a complaint; or simply want more information; contact our Privacy Compliance Officer using the button below:
Contact Us
or by mail at G-Mach Engineering Ltd: 7, 9 & 9a Beler Way, Leicester Rd Ind. Est. Melton Mowbray, Leicestershire, LE13 0DG, United Kingdom
